so he goes over to the creepy_crawly and he pulls it out the pool and one leg is broken .
that' why it wasn't moving .
the pump was good .
but he replaced the seal the o_rings .
and how much did he charge ?
a hundred and twenty dollars .
and how much would it been if we went and got the gauge and the and fixed the creepy_crawly up ?
the creepy_crawly would have been maybe thirty bucks if I would have gone .
but I didn't know it was broken .
and the gauge thing the pressure ?
the gauge thing he replaced it .
uh I don't know how much that cost me but uh the visit alone was sixty .
and then he replaced the o_rings which really .
this is the Bill guy ?
yeah Bill .
did you ask him about the pool heater ?
or you didn't ask ?
you know he said he said .
listen um (...) uh ...
because I told him about my brother_in_law and everything .
goes .
listen I guarantee you he' gonna get you a better price than my boss is gonna let you let me sell you one for .
and what about installing installing it ?
no installing if we have this guy .
or Paul .
yo no quiero contar con él .
I'll call .
with Paul ?
because then .
él se demora .
and he is he is going to school now .
and he has the ...
he means well pero when family gets put last .
the company .
the grass isn't growing here .
and where' the gak thing you're saying was coming out of it ?
look you see it ?
no .
coming out of the .
white little exhausts .
no not really .
if you stand up and look it looks like slime .
looks like gak .
but has it gone better since you cleaned the footer ?
no .
he says has to come over and do a um ...
+coil cleaning .
a coil cleaning .
but the guy that installed the antenna said that not to touch it that that' poisonous and corrosive and uh ...
ay .
Paul said .
no it' just dirt and and water that' accumulated .
it' not toxic .
it' not corrosive .
it' nothing .
hiss exagerado !
I have to jump in the pool tomorrow at some point .
I hope it' warm .
because I gotta to put the the drain the blocker on the drain so the creepy_crawly doesn't get stuck and ...
and it' clean ?
it' gonna be cold .
it' clean .
imit:crying I want the heater .
.
clears_throat .
would be nice .
it should be coming in soon .
ten to twelve days .
Wednesday ?
eight to fifteen days .
he they said ten to twelve .
eight to fifteen .
it said it on the package .
eight to fifteen business days .
mmhm .
today counts as a business day .
yeah .
so we went on Thursday ?
uh ...
yeah we went on Thursday .
yeah .
.
so today is the eighth .
today is the eighth so any time after this .
yeah .
what time do you have to be at the workshop tomorrow ?
eight o'clock in Miami_Springs .
what time do I have to leave ?
there' no traffic .
seven twenty leave at seven thirty .
did I tell you that Julie ' going ?
but does Julie know if you can apply then for mentoring points ?
Julie said you could .
so if you go to the workshop you can ?
she' mentoring .
so she' mentoring and she' gonna be able to count all the points .
yeah .
all the hours .
yeah but I think she' just going to scam it and uh you know mark the ones she' already done because there was a certain number that you had to have .
there' no way you can do ninety from now to March thirty_first unless you're sleeping with the person and living with the person .
maybe they'll the last batch .
yeah but I know that you had to input it prior to .
like now like they have like little deadlines that you have to input like the hours that you had before January .
you have to put the hours before January the hours before February the hours before March .
oh you just ninety hours of mentoring .
no hay duda de eso .
and the truth of the matter is you have .
no I know .
and I know I've done the ninety hours .
I just .
and I'm giving you mine .
mmhm no you can't give me yours .
I was telling Gloria .
no .
I will though .
um I was telling Gloria that after I stayed with Janet till ten o'clock at night you know and we're late and everything uh she e_mails me today .
I'm not gonna be able to video the second lesson again .
you know I'm just what I have .
I hate when people do that .
I don't know if I told you that .
and I just didn't respond .
and I told Gloria because .
Sunshine !
hundred percent if she' not gonna give herself a hundred percent ?
it' not worth it .
I have enough to do .
I've to work on the fricking formatting crap .
Sunshine be careful .
it was very minor what they told me I had to change .
what ?
centering a page .
margins a no sé qué on the appendix .
but you see what I'm saying is they should not give you because they've asked you to format a thousand different ways .
they should have one person at the end of the process once everything' approved um doing the formatting .
o_k you need to change this and this .
what that' what the college .
so should have one person in charge of of formatting .
in the college of education they hire Mrs_Dr_Blap to do that .
but they submitted my dissertation with those formatting issues because they knew that it would still pass for the defense .
some of the catches she didn't catch .
and she caught things that they didn't catch .
qué ?
I was looking today .
los varones estaban jugando fútbol .
y Maruja the girl from across the street .
oh .
+, was outside talking on the phone .
uhuh .
and I was watching this from Rosa' bedroom .
and uh I would see that she would be looking at them and talking on the phone and ...
they would catch passes in front of her .
when have they ever decided to play football here ?
two weeks ago .
when we had the music playing .
mmhm .
I was thinking that I don't know Mary siempre se fastidia getting all the drinks .
we should get .
did you saw that orange Gatorade thing from when you're coaching ?
yeah .
we should every now and then have .
why what' wrong with Mary ?
que these kids need to drink .
and they probably go into Mary' house I think all the time and drink .
we need to be supplying our them with drinks .
when I was a kid you know we used to do ?
we used to get the hose and drink from the hose .
if they're too prissy to drink from the hose then let them go inside and get drinks .
o_k they have not .
I'm not going to be supplying little thing .
they the next thing you know I'd be taking pictures of them as they're playing basketball .
.
and he is a .
uh .
my grass isn't growing .
I'm not happy .
you know why ?
because these trees block the sunlight .
and why do the why does it have to be grass here ?
I like it grass .
what else would you recommend ?
pebbles mulch .
mulch do you think I should ?
I have two bags of mulch I can lay .
then do it because ahí no va a crecer nada .
look it it it the shade is completely covering it .
I have hope .
and you never know if birds have eaten the seeds .
Sunshine !
no .
bird can't even see the seeds .
they don't see worms either yet they eat them .
yeah they see the worms .
they dig into the ground to get a worm .
she has something in her tail .
y Rosa hoy dijo que la iba a bañar .
Sunshine .
ella luce limpia ?
kiss .
no .
ah .
she hasn't been bathed .
she took her in the morning like she was gonna bathe her .
milagro que Marga hasn't come out .
como así .
huh ?
she' coming ?
eh ?
no .
I think they're all enjoying t_v .
I didn't think anybody was gonna be at work today .
Sunshine get away from that cactus .
ah ?
I thought was just gonna be me and Rosa .
and I even told Rosa I was gonna get there at tennish .
pero no hubo tráfico so I was able to go straight .
and and that' it .
go in F_I_U .
and picking up the thing .
there' no traffic .
was she there before you ?
no but Susie was .
no I'm saying Susie .
Susie wa() yeah when I got in the door was unlocked and how weird .
but wasn't she supposed to be out ?
I thought everybody was gonna be out today .
that' what I had heard that everybody was out .
es que she gave everybody the day off except for herself .
y ...
+, which is fine .
we made a lot of progress .
y cómo te fue el día ?
all day .
the morning was getting ready for the meeting .
basically it was C_C' integrates .
I gave her the ideas .
pero she ...
+modified them .
+, complicated them .
she C_C_ed them .
if that means complicate then yeah .
you know these are meant to be for teacher assistants and they're supposed to be non_threatening low_prep you know emphasizing .
and I had told her you know do something on conservation because there' water ...
I given her .
long story short it was very complicated so ...
I had already gone through them because supposedly that' what I was gonna do yesterday .
so then in the morning I went through them I made copies of everything and then I also gave .
for example one of the reviewers had recommended a book in the lesson of displacement where the water is displaced ...
mmhm .
+, uh called the crow and the pitcher .
it' an Aesop fable .
Aesop .
.
eso mismo .
Aesop .
A_E_S_O_P .
it has an A .
Aesop' fables .
A Aesop .
Aesop' fable .
you know the crow and the pitcher ?
anyway it has to do with a crow who wants to get uh drink some water from a pitcher .
but his beak doesn't go inside .
so he needs putting little stones in until the water rises enough he can drink it .
and the thing is using your wit to get whatever .
but it' a lesson on displacement which is exactly the second lesson .
Ruby used it .
so I showed .
and you went to work with those shoes ?
I thought I was alone .
and did she say anything ?
no pero Rosa las chancletas .
they're cute .
they match my ear_rings .
Rosa said chancletas ?
no but she was talking to me about the other day .
and I was like .
they call me Hialeah when I wear chancletas .
it' cute .
like very cute .
it' a .
fíjate .
you know um Rosa said that ...
uh did Janet leave those shoes ?
and they said .
no I think they're Mum' .
why ?
because they're cute .
so she' got her eye on them .
?
.
which ones the ropy ones that are kind of high ?
yes .
you know actually I bought them when I got them about a week ago I was gonna get them for her .
and I got them .
Sunshine whatever your name is cat get out .
I'm just happy they're alive .
I really thought it was them .
yesterday with the vulture was disgusting .
and you know everyone that comes the guy Marco the guy from the satellite dish the guy from the thing they all step on my cactus garden .
I'm making I'm starting to think either one of two things either I have to remove the the hose from there (...) or remove my cactus garden .
mind but it' so pretty you know ?
it' very infrequent that people come .
well now when we put the the heater ...
it' just been ...
that' one more person only .
no te vas a morir .
hey you mind if I trample all your cactus ?
have you noticed that uh ...
aquí viene Marga .
Margarita .
tell her to turn on the light .
no .
she didn't see us .
she looked in the kitchen and ...
se fue .
let her know we're here though .
here she comes .
yeah hold on to that .
hi mama .
where have you been ?
I was swimming .
but I couldn't hear you .
oh I didn't hear you .
good job you closed .
mami !
Marga close the door with the handle .
really the crazy tiger was outside ?
turn the handle .
there we go .
you gonna sit with us ?
yeah .
what were you watching on t_v ?
ah .
.
what ?
Hannah_Montana .
Hannah_Montana ?
groan mami ?
yes ?
I'm putting my foot up for a reason .
put your foot up .
you have cute toes .
they look like dad' .
uh uh .
dile como mami .
do your toes look like mami or papi ?
mami .
yeah .
and papi .
no .
mami' .
mami .
yeah .
I wanna play over there .
where ?
now go there a little bit .
.
you know where the cats were ?
they were under the deck .
where ?
down here under this .
?
I guess they were trying to find protection .
protection ?
don't you remember those shells when they need a protection ?
yeah .
?
the one inside the shell ?
Sunshine !
shh !
.
you know when she is inside she barks to come out .
I guess .
and when she is outside she barks to come in .
well she is a teenager .
nunca satisfecha .
where is our teenager that should be taking care of her ?
where is Rosa ?
he' following me .
me ?
.
!
whoa !
.
was that toy in your ?
or was it in Tina' house ?
.
it was in my bunkbed .
it was in my bunkbed first but it was in in Tina' house .
Marga you know how to turn on that light ?
.
inside turn it on ?
go turn it on .
you just click it .
yeah open the door and turn it on .
leave the door open !
do you think he did the handles reverse on purpose ?
why ?
hmm I don't know .
that was my next question why did he do it ?
I don't think he did it reversed .
I did it .
gracias .
thank you close the door .
I mean that' easily corrected .
ah doesn't matter .
.
I'm used to it like that so ...
jinx .
.
o_k .
are you gonna get your microphone ?
you're the contestant ?
tell Rosa to get Sunshine .
she' not gonna get her .
open the door for Sunshine .
Sunshine !
Sunshine go inside go inside !
o_k .
olvídate Marga .
is she coming ?
welcome to American_Idol .
my name is (...) .
Danny ?
Emily ?
my name is Emily .
hi Emily .
what you gonna sing for us today ?
I'm gonna sing ...
?
I'm gonna sing you .
you're gonna sing me a song ?
.
but you're Simon ?
o_k .
.
clap .
very nice .
you go to Hollywood doll !
yeah I say yes .
.
tell the next person to come out .
Sunshine !
whistle .
tell get Rosa Sunshine ' gonna vomit again grass .
Rosa !
hi welcome to American_Idol .
my name is Mirabelle .
ay .
Rebecca ?
oh I thought Rebecca was the other one .
o_k .
what are you gonna sing for us today ?
no it was Emily .
I know but my paper said Rebecca .
I'm gonna sing I'm gonna sing .
Sunshine !
I like Hannah_Montana .
I love Hannah_Montana doll .
.
can you see ?
yeah .
.
ooh .
gotta dance when I sing .
that was beautiful dancing .
.
could double as a superstar .
a little bit .
just a little Ryan ?
but I wanna hear you .
cough only a little bit .
o_k alright .
well you know what I got a surprise for you doll .
you're gonna Hollywood !
I say yes .
.
whistle .
!
Rosa !
pretty good .
call Rosa !
very good .
.
call Rosa .
Margarita llama a Rosa .
are you taking care of ..?
sí go get Rosa .
llama a tu hermana .
there' a baby ...
yes go get Rosa .
sí llama a tu hermana .
Rosa .
tell her to come get her dog because she is eating grass again .
yeah .
eating grass again .
to get her .
what ?
to babysit her dog .
llama la .
babysit your dog .
?
when is the competition ?
.
are you going at home ?
yes .
no ?
.
I'm talking to the maths department .
sorry about that .
Sunshine !
no .
ah they don't need .
ah Dad !
April seventh to tenth ?
mmm !
April what ?
mommy I need to do peepee .
Rosa lleva a Marga al baño .
apúrate .
Rosa forget your dog .
.
run !
go .
close the door .
.
that' gonna bruise tomorrow when you dress .
Rosa is she doing peepee ?
.
I thought she just wanted the bathroom ?
Margarita ?
yeah before .
Rosa took her .
yo no la he llevado .
Laura turned in her magnet unit today .
bueno no .
she turned it in a few weeks ago .
but today we went over it .
today she turned in lesson three and four .
lesson two three and four actually .
and Susie crucificó la primera lección .
merecía un poco de crucificción .
sí ?
yeah but still .
you know you gotta be loyal to who' been with you .
I mean I'm thinking coño if I'm not here what the hell would happen to me ?
sí pero ...
I mean a a ti te pagan para que tú hagas quality work .
and if you're not doing quality work para qué te van a pagar ?
no but it wasn't misquality either .
it' just like some things er ...
the second lesson was very good .
it was weird because the second lesson ...
I didn't even look at the third and fourth .
pero today I had done all my little integrals .
and then we went over the magnet lessons .
so it it takes all day .
yeah .
el trabajito que me mandaron a mí se demoró bastante tiempo .
you need to submit the P_O .
it' two hundred bucks .
but I don't know I don't have a P_O .
where am I gonna get a P_O from ?
they show is my job complete because I think they were gonna your job is complete for this section .
what the heck ?
so is the game over ?
they're arguing about basketball .
they're playing basketball now ?
thought they were playing football .
yeah .
no basketball .
well apparently somebody made a really important shot and ...
do you think it was Guapo ?
no .
who' screaming again ?
was that Rachel ?
eh ?
is that Rachel screaming ?
no sé .
hay hay bastantes de ellos ahí .
lo ignoré completamente hoy .
eh ?
lo ignoré completamente .
tú sabes lo que me gusta ?
el que él va a estar con todos esos muchachos el año que viene .
mmhm .
y él no va a entrar .
ay please .
and he knows Bill_Lloyd .
and he knows Rosa and Kathy and ...
and he knows Rosa' friends .
Rosa and Kathy are gonna be juniors .
uh .
hi !
wow did you do peepee ?
are you ready for your song ?
yes .
what' your name ?
my name is cough .
it says Little_Bo_Peep .
no that' not what is says here on mine .
mine says Grandpa_Joe Pancake_Joe .
that' Guapo .
Pancake_Joe is Guapo .
woah mine is ...
let me ask .
laugh .
Emily .
hi Emily .
hi Emily how are you ?
good .
are you gonna sing us some Hannah_Montana doll ?
cough .
chuckle you're thinking ?
wanna be a rock star ?
Kathy the other Kathy .
Dutch .
oh Dutch .
o_k .
cough .
oh you mean ?
yes .
.
Papi' ringtone ?
o_k .
.
yeah yeah I know .
clap .
very very nice .
and do you think you're gonna go to Hollywood ?
I think .
I think yes too .
Margarita !
Ryan ?
she' gonna Hollywood .
Margarita ?
I'm not Margarita now .
Emily ?
.
did she wash her hair ?
bye_bye bye_bye .
and did you make .
bye_bye .
your mum mentioned .
for us not to make her feel better she brought .
Papa !
to guilt us into not saying .
Chinese brothers !
Jonas_Brothers ?
where ?
I'm gonna sing .
o_k sing the Jonas_Brothers .
o_k .
are you Joe_Jonas ?
Kevin ?
.
uhuh I put .
the D_J has arrived .
I I put in ear ear_worm in my studios .
what ?
uh if you look me in the eye .
tell me that you love me .
everything' alright .
.
sorry .
that was the best one of the day .
you're going to Hollywood Emily !
I think you're gonna win .
you're gonna be the next American_Idol .
?
I loved it .
I loved the screaming part .
it was a lot of emotion .
you did perfect .
it was it was my dream of ...
what' your dream ?
no it was not my secret .
it' your dream ?
.
is your dream to be American_Idol ?
Paula !
I'm Paula ?
I've been promoted ?
my little baby Simon .
going from Simon to Paula .
that means I'm positive .
Simon .
ha you're negative .
I'm Simon ?
you're negative .
hello .
Simon ?
I'm Simon and you were awful .
uh_oh he' lying .
chuckle .
give me a job !
give her the job !
o_k you're going to Hollywood .
but you better impress .
.
Emily (...) Emily !
chuckle .
Emily call Margarita !
oh um ...
Margarita ?
my daughter .
Rosa .
where is she ?
I don't know .
uh ...
she looks like you though .
cough this ?
Julie asked me ...
my dad .
.
gasp you are Marga ?
you're pretending ?
Margarita ?
I'm not Margarita .
I thought you're pretending ?
my doll is named Margarita .
oh yeah mm .
oh .
.
well let me listen to Papi a second .
Julie .
Julie asked me .
she goes .
oh what are you doing for spring break ?
are you guys going out of town ?
and then I said .
well Chloe is she' going to New_York .
.
I was thinking of the Friday of spring break to take the girls over to Chubby_Cheese .
don't know .
she gave us the gift certificate .
bye_bye .
bye guys bye Simon !
can it be the Monday or the Tuesday ?
then I'm here .
the Tuesday is your graduation your your defense .
bye Simon !
at ten o'clock and I'm going back to work .
lose the day .
why ?
I'm hoping she'll I'll get the day at the end .
or take the rest of the day off .
hi guys !
hi Marga come here !
I'm not Marga .
can you call Marga ?
she looks like you .
Marga !
hi .
she did say .
are you Marga ?
.
she said if your wife' alright with it .
Mommy !
oh Mommy !
qué ?
oh you call me Mommy .
you're Marga ?
yeah .
?
sing the next .
no I need to ask you about the soup you mean .
.
I need the recipe .
are you not at all ?
.
what do you mean ?
bye_bye little kitty .
oh we went to the movies .
she took Julie .
Julie asked her .
oh how are you ?
.
how was your weekend ?
she goes .
oh it was great .
.
I went to the movies .
Ulrika .
and we went to Chubby_Cheese .
Ulrika ?
como Ulrika .
ay qué linda .
aw .
.
il la dijo .
you are !
.
if you are !
no .
it' already it was already closed .
cough .
because she likes to sleep .
did you talk to Julie ?
she put it in the boca .
she was Jessica' monkey .
gasp no no no boca no !
no she licked it .
no !
now slidie .
yawn .
hello !
.
pizza' here .
speaking of slides .
how you gonna pay for it ?
slide !
I hope Rosa did it on the credit card .
did you credit card ?
.
no it' already online .
oh yeah ?
now she' sliding backwards .
and the tip ?
tell Rosa the pizza' here .
Marga tell Rosa the pizza' here .
clears_throat Rosa the pizza' here !
so was faster than thirty minutes .
Rosa the pizza' here !
Rosa !
chuckle .
she' asleep .
tell her if she doesn't go there' no pizza .
Rosa the pizza' .
.
where you didn't put it on the credit card ?
no .
cough .
we're kinda connected right now .
I have ten dollars in my purse .
I don't have any money in my purse .
put it on the credit card ?
I thought he was gonna she put it on the credit card .
.
come on .
go can you answer the door ?
he might go away and there goes your pizza .
not my pizza .
I'll chase him down .
.
turn the lights on .
I've ten .
that' all I got .